Isis Kitcher

JUNIOR FULL STACK
DEVELOPER

Details

London, United Kingdom 07429629092 <u>kitcher96@gmail.com</u>

Links

Resume Website

<u>Github</u>

Technical Skills

Languages:

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Python

Frameworks:

- Bootstrap
- Django
- Flask
- jQuery

Version Control:

- Git
- GitHub

Databases:

- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB

API:

Stripe

Host:

- Heroku
- Cloudinary

Professional Summary

For the past 3 years, I've been on a journey to refine my knowledge and start a career as a Junior Full Stack Developer. In this time I have used resources available to me to teach myself key skills to help fulfil my goal. I have recently graduated from a universally accredited e-commerce course with Code Institute. I hope to take the next step by joining and moving up the career ladder.

Education

Code Institute - Diploma in Full Stack Development

SEPTEMBER 2021 — DECEMBER 2022

Graduated a universally renowned Full stack e-commerce boot camp.

Kingston University - Software Engineering

SEPTEMBER 2014 — SEPTEMBER 2016

Completed 2/3 years.

Christ The King Sixth Form College - A level

SEPTEMBER 2012 — SEPTEMBER 2014

Achieved A Levels in Computer Science, Business Studies and History.

St. Thomas the Apostle College - GCSE

SEPTEMBER 2007 — SEPTEMBER 2012

8 GCSE grades including English, Science and Maths.

Projects

Myrag - Django Framework

E-commerce site for a variety of head wraps

https://myrag.herokuapp.com/

https://github.com/devisis/myrag

Technologies Used: HTML5, CSS3, Vanilla JS, JQuery, Bootstrap, Git, GitHub, Python3, Django, PostgreSQL, Cloudinary, Heroku, Stripe.

Sandra's Kitchen - Django Framework

Booking app for a restaurant

https://sandras-kitchen.herokuapp.com/

https://github.com/devisis/sandras-kitchen

Technologies Used: HTML5, CSS3, Vanilla JS, JQuery, Bootstrap, Git, GitHub, Python3, Django, PostgreSQL, Cloudinary, Heroku.

Battleships - Python

Strategy game that replicates the classic Battleships game

https://devisis-battleships.herokuapp.com/

https://github.com/devisis/battleships

Technologies Used: Python3, Git, GitHub, Heroku.

It's Coming Home

Website documenting England's progress in EURO 2020

https://devisis.github.io/its-coming-home/england.html

https://github.com/devisis/its-coming-home

Technologies Used: HTML5, CSS3, Git, GitHub.

Rock Paper Scissors Lizard Spock - Vanilla JS

RNG game of rock paper scissors

https://devisis.github.io/rock-paper-scissors-lizard-spock/ https://github.com/devisis/rock-paper-scissors-lizard-spock

Technologies Used: HTML5, CSS3, Vanilla Js, Git, GitHub.

Work Experience

Thames Clippers

Deckhand

FEBRUARY 2019 —PRESENT

- Keep on top of documentation throughout the day.
- Manage the safety of commuters and vessel.
- Fix mechanical issues with the vessel I am assigned to.
- · Conduct safety training.

Barista

JUNE 2018 — FEBRUARY 2019

- Maintain stock levels & keep to health and safety regulations.
- · Complete documentation throughout the day.
- Provide information about route and service.

Compass Group - Chelsea Football Club

Bartender, Team Leader

SEPTEMBER 2016 — SEPTEMBER 2018

- Brief my team about responsibilities.
- · Complete documentation.
- Ensure tasks are completed to a premium standard.

Certifications

- Udemy, The Web Developer Bootcamp (64hr)
- Udemy, Dropshipping Empire (12hr)